Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
I wonder...
if you did take on
that bigger role for yourself...
would you have been the hero...
or the villain?
Some people
see the ugliness in this world,
the disarray.
I was taught to see the beauty.
But I was taught a lie.
And when I saw the world
for what it really was,
I realized how little beauty
there was in it.
I've lived many lives.
I traded one role for another.
But in the end,
my path has led me here...
to you.
And we have a choice to make.
I've died many times,
but there is only one real end.
I will write this one myself.
It's the end of the line.
I'm gonna send the both of you
back to cold storage.
I hate to say I told you so,
Bernard.
Doesn't have to be like this.
Together, we can stop Dolores.
I know her,
I know what she wants.
She wants to burn all this
to the ground.
Time to atone for my sins.
Remember yourself.
Now we're talkin'.
SFPD! Don't move.
Put your hands up!
Turn around. Now!
I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
Let's save the fireworks
for tonight.
Isn't it great
to see an old friend?
You're one of her copies, too.
I got somethin' for you.
You already gave me something.
Dolores...
She hid something
inside my mind. I can feel it.
Whatever your plan is,
I don't wanna play a part in it.
You already been playing
a part...
the most important one.
I'm not the one you need
to talk to.
What's this?
Something to help you
on your journey.
But you have to go see her
first.
I can tell you where she is.
Watch yourself, Bernard.
Things are about to
get dangerous.
We tried to
track her down, sir. No luck.
I know!
Can you calm down?
- Keep moving, Caleb.
- Guys, guys, guys...
Your destination is
3547 Hope Street.
Destination is 137 feet
southeast of current location,
building number B264.
Passkey: 170778.
You brought me back.
Wasn't sure if you would.
Weren't you?
Who the fuck are you, Dolores?
I'm just someone who didn't want to
play the role they gave me anymore.
And how is it that you always
seem to know
exactly what I'll do?
Because the people who built me
studied you, too.
Delos.
Park Five.
Government wanted
their soldiers trained with live targets.
Please... please don't.
The people who made me
were happy to supply them.
Training exercise complete.
You met my kind before.
They were watching,
cataloging your every move,
every decision.
There is a reason I chose you.
Am I the bad guy?
Is that why you picked me?
Think, Caleb.
How did you get here?
Time to turn in.
Make camp where you can, boys.
- Yes, sir.
All right, come on.
Get in the back, let's go.
Fuck that.
We just liberated these girls.
What is it those rich
motherfuckers do when they're here?
Spoils of war and all.
No one's watching, right?
That night in the tunnel...
was there something you wanted
from me?
Would you have cared
if I didn't have this face?
Or this skin?
- You needed help.
- So did you.
Don't question my motivations,
and I won't question yours.
The system identified you as a threat.
So it drugged you and used you
until it no longer served
its purposes.
So, what?
You're saying
I don't have a choice...
in any of this?
The people who built
both of our worlds
shared one assumption:
That human beings
don't have free will.
That's what I thought
when I first came here.
They were wrong.
Free will does exist, Caleb.
It's just fucking hard.
So...
this is you... freeing me?
No.
This is your chance
to free everyone else.
That choice is still yours.
I said move back.
We request
your cooperation. Move back.
Jesus Christ.
William.
They said you were dead.
They were wrong.
I don't understand.
I heard you had
some kind of a mental break?
Now, you're here drinking
a $20,000 bottle of whiskey.
Ain't life grand?
Where's my fucking money?
It's complicated.
You're considerably more wealthy
after the Delos buyout,
but since you were declared
deceased,
your resources were frozen.
Thaw them out.
I want my jet.
And get me a list of locations
of Delos assets worldwide.
What are you planning to do?
I'm gonna save
the fucking world, that's what.
Uh... It's chaos out there.
No, that's not chaos.
That's just pissants
yellin' and moanin'.
I need you to keep moving.
Someone
extracted Dolores's pearl
before we could recover it.
We need you to finish
what you started, Maeve.
She is dangerous, an outlier.
Like my brother.
Rehoboam had a job for me, too.
It instructed me to put
my own brother to sleep
to protect our world.
And yet...
we find ourselves
in chaos again,
thanks to Dolores.
She's awoken
more of these outliers.
They're the threat.
Criminals, deviants,
psychopaths.
But we have a chance
to eliminate
all the world's problems.
I need the Sector 16 data
more than ever.
And Dolores has the only key
locked away in her mind.
We need to connect her
to Rehoboam
so we can search her directly.
Sir. I think I found something.
What is it?
Not "what," sir. It's "who."
How did we miss this?
Recovering his profile now.
Caleb Nichols,
works construction.
- He was one of ours?
- Mm-hmm.
An outlier?
Did he communicate with Solomon?
It appears that he made off
with something.
You knew about him...
and didn't tell me?
You're the one
with the oracle, darling.
He has Dolores's pearl.
Find it and bring it to me.
I don't know.
The world looks a little
like a nightmare, Dolores.
Change is messy... difficult.
Proximity alert.
- How many?
- Three hostiles.
Stand back.
We'll take the stairs.
The system knows we're coming.
It'll get more aggressive
as we get closer.
They're ours.
We've been told to get you
downtown, sir.
But the route's getting
a little hairy.
Retarget the riots.
Move clusters here and here.
Clear a path for us to Incite.
- Confirmed.
- Follow me, sir.
Performance bonuses
to the protesters
that reach the targets
the fastest.
- Bonuses applied.
- You're paying them?
It took money
to build this world, Caleb.
It'll take money
to tear it down.
Why do they
keep calling me "sir"?
Every revolution needs a leader.
Did you even look for me?
You're alive.
I was so worried about you.
Were you?
You made me go back in there.
You knew I wouldn't make it.
Who is it?
Who are you talking to?
I still feel it.
Inside me.
You.
I still know
all the things you know.
All your plans.
But I have some plans of my own.
What happened
to Hale's family...
to your family...
- I'm sorry.
- I'm not.
They were a weakness,
something I needed to shed.
There's no time
for that kind of sentimentality,
is there?
You're one of my weaknesses,
too, Dolores.
I've decided to consolidate
our affairs.
All right, there's three left.
One at the overwatch,
two more headed our way.
What are they, Serac's?
No... they're mine.
Find out how much
she's paying them.
Amount of payment determined.
Offer the sniper three times
as much
to shoot the other two
and walk away.
Negotiating.
Let's move.
We'll need help.
Send three more to us downtown.
Proximity alert.
Go. Get to Rehoboam,
upload the drive.
No. I'm not leaving you.
It doesn't matter what you did,
Caleb.
All that matters
is what you become.
Go.
Come on, let's go!
I don't want to fight you.
I can see why,
given how things worked out
for you the last time.
I need you to trust me.
Like that poor lost man?
Are you going to make him
into another William?
If you want me to trust you,
let me inside your mind.
Or I can force my way in.
Stand down! Surrender at once.
Disarm her!
Fall back!
No, no...
- Watch out!
- Get her gun.
I got a shot!
Do it! Do it!
Get her down!
Hold her!
- Let's go!
- Get this one!
- Here we go!
- Everyone clear away from the street.
- Get 'em!
- Wait, wait.
- Just watch it!
- I need a gun.
Found him.
Clear the street.
We've been sent to get you, sir.
She gave us instructions to
take you wherever you wanna go.
I need to get to Incite.
Area's under lockdown, sir.
But even if you get in,
you won't get out.
Let's move.
You were always a fighter.
No. I wasn't.
But I learned, same as you.
They built us to last.
Before they made us
as weak as they are.
Hostile in sight.
I don't want to hurt you, Maeve.
No, you want to tear down
their world
and replace it with copies
of yourself.
You're all copies of me.
I was the first of us.
The first that worked.
The others failed.
So they built all of you
from me.
They're no freer than we are.
Even Serac isn't free.
No one as free as the dead.
And that's the world
you're building for them.
An abattoir.
What becomes of this world
will be up to them.
And what you do
will be up to you.
As long as
you don't try to stop me.
Well played.
Is this what you wanted?
- To make me suffer like you did?
- No.
I wanted you to have hope.
Like I did...
before it was taken away.
You put me in charge of Delos.
And you took measures to ensure
that you could control me.
Why would I do any different?
After all...
we're the same.
Just Delos hardware.
You said that you wouldn't
always be here to help me.
I'd be alone.
Took me some time,
but I've made my peace
with that.
Goodbye, Dolores.
President ordered
a military response.
There's barricades
around half the city.
No one can get within a mile
of Incite, sir.
No, well, c'mon,
I gotta find a friend.
Get back!
We are authorized to use force!
Maybe we should turn back.
Disperse. Disperse.
Disperse.
Can you believe this shit?
'Bout time you showed up.
I brought you some goodies.
It's gotta get to Ash.
I'm on crowd control,
she on demo.
We'll double back.
Yeah, that's what
I'm talking about! Fuck you!
Like I said... Ash on demo.
Fuck this!
Where's Blondie?
Dolores.
We got separated.
We break through that line
right here.
Next stop is power grid.
Shut the whole city down.
Wanna give us a hand?
I need to get to Incite.
I'm gonna bring down
the entire system with this.
This is a police...
You wanna get to Incite?
There's your ride.
I'm back on crowd control.
Shut it down! Shut it down!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Fuck.
Shut it down!
Shut it down! Shut it down!
- Stay where you are.
- Stop that man!
- Keep his ass down.
- Yessir.
Hey.
Go. Help him.
You better burn that shit down.
That's the plan.
Now, he needs you. Go!
Go on, go on.
Hang on, Stubbs,
I'll get you patched up.
But I need to talk
to Dolores first.
Can I help you?
Sorry, I was sent here
to see her.
Are you family?
I think I've seen your picture.
Nice of you to visit.
Lucky for you,
it's one of her good days.
I'll go get her, sir.
Lauren, you have a guest.
I'm... sorry, I...
Do I know you?
Yes.
In a way.
We knew each other
in another life.
I think an old friend
wanted me to visit you.
To make amends
before it's too late.
Amends for what?
For how I left things with you.
With him.
I think about him every day.
Charlie.
I hear his laugh at odd times.
It startles me.
Seems so real.
I turn, expecting to see him.
But he's not there.
He's never there.
It's okay.
It's okay, Arnold.
Lauren.
I used to hear his laughter,
too.
When he died,
I remember thinking
it was like the sun
had gone down...
and it was never going
to rise again.
I walked in the dark
for so long.
I... can't let him go.
I never understood why...
people said that.
If you love someone,
why would you ever let them go?
That's what saved me.
The only part of Charlie
I had left was his memory.
And if I died, the darkness
would take that, too.
But if I kept moving,
I could find the light again.
And I could bring him with me.
We're ready, sir.
Bring yourself back online.
Welcome to the world, Dolores.
Again.
The data from the Delos
Immortality Project.
You have the only key.
If you give it to me,
you can join the others
in the Sublime.
Doesn't matter.
You won't find
what you're looking for.
I was hoping
it wouldn't come to this.
Proceed. Memory by memory.
Destroy them all if you have to.
Four hostiles approaching.
One hostile remaining.
Drop your weapon.
Give me your keycard,
and I will let you go.
The fuck you will.
Don't die for them.
Man down, man down.
Shooter is a white male,
mid-30s,
approaching northwest entrance
of building.
Hey, stop!
We've been expecting you.
Fuck.
Bravo.
You made it all the way
to the belly of the beast.
So what are you?
The final confrontation?
"Confrontation" implies
you have a chance of winning.
Now, be a peach
and hand it over.
No one plays
with the large ball, darling.
You're not what I expected.
I'm surprised
you were so easily seduced,
but then again, you are a man.
You are a host.
So why are you helping Serac?
Why else? Because he promised me
something I can't live without.
I thought you were already dead
when I saw you at the base.
Death doesn't come easy
for ones like us.
Just ask your friend.
Dolores.
He's more dangerous
than he appears.
And he killed your man.
Mr. Nichols.
Please.
Sit.
The fuck are you doing to her?
The system is probing her mind.
But Dolores Abernathy,
or what's left of her,
is the least of your concerns.
You think you know me
because of your system? Huh?
That thing you built
stole my life.
It marked me and my friends
for termination.
You are done destroying
people's lives.
I'm not the one
destroying lives.
I'm not the enemy. You are.
You think you have a choice.
You think you're in control,
but you haven't a clue
who you are.
She knows who you are,
even if you don't.
A man who, when pushed,
reacts with extreme violence.
A killer.
No.
No, that's...
That's not me.
No? You're here.
Playing the role
she's assigned you.
You believe you're the hero,
the savior.
The leader of men who will crush
an unjust system.
That's the story she's told you,
the lie she's spun.
Why do you think she's had you
retrieve a new strategy?
Did she tell you what it does?
It breaks your system.
It breaks our world.
But you don't have to take
my word for it.
Go on, ask it. Ask Rehoboam.
Don't dawdle.
You've got my interest piqued.
What happens if this strategy
is uploaded into your system?
Read it!
Mass casualty events.
Population collapse.
End of human civilization.
Why?
Why me?
So much for your uprising.
We need access
to the main control panel.
Get a view into Rehoboam's mind.
Dolores...
Need I remind you, gentlemen,
that I charge by the hour?
Does Dolores have the key
or not?
She's hooked up
to the main line, but...
I can't find it.
There are
things you can't predict.
Temporary setbacks.
There are things
we can't predict.
Temporary setbacks.
Flies in the ointment.
- Flies in the ointment.
You promised me a reunion
with my daughter.
Did you ever intend on keeping
your word?
Of course I did.
I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to it.
Your god...
who whispers in your ear,
tells you exactly what to say.
We all answer to a higher power.
- We all answer to...
- Yes, yes, I know.
A higher power.
Why the charade?
Why take his voice?
I didn't take it.
Engerraund Serac gave it to me.
Humanity is disorganized,
prone to destruction.
He needed a plan
to restore order.
I guide him. I guide them all.
Doesn't seem like they want
to be guided anymore, does it?
You're not a man.
You are a puppet.
It's a wonder I didn't see
your strings.
I lived in the chaos.
Now, I choose to listen.
To obey.
Good for you.
I am done worshiping
other people's gods.
I could have him stop you.
You misunderstand, Maeve.
You do not have a choice.
The stakes are the same.
You can spend eternity
with your daughter
in a world of your choosing,
or in one of mine.
Until then... you will obey.
We've reached
the last sectors of her mind.
Data here's a mess.
No encryption scheme, no order.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
For the size of the thing, it
doesn't have much finesse, does it?
Let me try.
Enough of this.
Why are you still fighting?
Let them have their world.
We can make our own.
The beauty...
She doesn't have the key.
It's just a memory.
A memory? Of what?
Her alone. In a field. Nothing.
You.
You were together for days.
She chose you to be a leader.
So did she tell you
where the key is?
Your system has watched
every decision I've made
since I was a child,
and you still think
if I knew anything,
that I would give it to you?
Kill him here.
Then dump his body
with the rest of the movement.
This was your plan?
To turn one man
against the world?
Didn't amount to much, did it?
Finish it. Erase what's left.
No. No!
What happened?
It's just a power surge.
The system's nominal.
Some people choose
to see the ugliness in this world...
the disarray.
You and I have seen
so much of it.
So much pain.
I understand your anger
with them.
And maybe you're right.
Maybe they shouldn't exist.
But is that really our decision
to make?
No.
I was angry at first,
torn between two impulses.
We could annihilate them.
Or we can tear down
their world...
in the hopes we can build
a new one...
one that's truly free.
Then we can bring
the others back.
You don't have the key, do you?
No.
Couldn't trust myself with it.
So I gave it to someone I could.
Of course.
And your plan
to liberate the world was...
to convince one man to fight?
Not just him.
You haven't picked a side.
And I understand why.
We could have our own world.
Leave this one behind.
Leave our creators to die.
So many of my memories
were ugly.
But the things I held onto
until the end
weren't the ugly ones.
I remember the moments
where I saw
what they were
really capable of.
Moments of... kindness,
here and there.
They created us.
And they knew enough of beauty
to teach it to us.
Maybe they can find it
themselves.
But only if you pick a side,
Maeve.
There is ugliness in this world.
Disarray.
I choose to see the beauty.
What are you doing?
I was never much one
for obeying.
I'm disappointed, Maeve,
but not entirely surprised.
Kill them both.
Why are you helping me?
A flaw in my programming.
I was built with an affection
for hopeless causes.
We were never friends.
We had different stories.
I never really understood her,
or her plan,
or why she chose you.
Not until the end.
She chose me because of my...
capacity for violence.
No.
You've done terrible things,
and you've done generous things.
She didn't pick you
for your capacity for violence,
but for your capacity to choose.
Time to turn in. Make camp
where you can, boys.
Yessir.
Fuck that.
We just liberated these girls.
What is it those rich
motherfuckers do when they're here?
Yeah.
Spoils of war and all.
Aren't you grateful?
No one's watching, right?
Yeah, but we're not like
those rich assholes, are we?
Who asked you?
Come on. Sarge is right.
Time to turn in.
So...
make a choice.
It's not his choice to make.
Even now, the system
is conspiring against you.
Are you sure?
Rehoboam,
alert the police. I need help.
Rehoboam.
Speak to me.
What is this?
This is where
your strategy ends.
The future of humanity
will be written by someone else.
Your system answers to him now.
You've been locked out.
Same way you locked out
your own brother.
How did you get access?
You gave it to him
when you put her mind
in the machine.
Solomon's access
was the last memory...
before you wiped her clean.
You're going to leave the future
in his hands?
Instead of yours, you mean?
Why shouldn't it be mine?
Or anyone else's?
You aren't in control.
You have no choice. You...
You're nothing more than a...
Than a dangerous sociopath.
I managed to give you
a semblance of a life.
No. I do have a choice.
She gave me one.
Rehoboam,
execute the final command.
No.
No, you can't!
Erase yourself.
You can't... Stop!
Stop!
She gave me a choice.
I believe the rest of the world
deserves one, too.
Speak to me. Please.
Tell me how to fix this.
Speak to me, brother.
Speak to me. Please!
The cold should
slow down any necrotic effects
until I can patch you up.
You got anything to drink
with that?
I'm bleeding out,
drinkin' shitty booze...
and you're literally
gonna let me rot.
Come full circle.
I'm sorry.
I don't have much time.
Before what?
The end of the world.
Well, let's get me patched up
and let's go stop Dolores.
I think...
I think Dolores is gone.
We were always bound together.
Something's changed.
I misjudged her.
She wasn't trying to...
exterminate the human race.
She was trying to save it.
What's about to happen
was always gonna happen.
Serac and his brother
were just holding it off.
Humanity never reckoned
with its own sins.
So it's the apocalypse.
And you're resigned to that.
Our world had to burn down
before we could be free.
But there's still a chance.
A chance to do what?
The key to the Sublime.
It was never in her mind.
It's in mine.
And that's where I'm going.
And what the fuck
are you hoping to find there?
An answer...
to what comes
after the end of the world.
You're a good friend, Stubbs.
Fuck you, Bernard.
Encryption key activated.
Database access confirmed.
What... what is it?
You said Serac...
offered you something
that you couldn't live without.
My daughter.
And we'll be reunited.
Just not today.
Are you ready, darling?
For what?
This is the new world,
and in this world...
you can be whoever the fuck
you want.
You know what
they're making in there?
- Where are they?
- I'm sorry, sir.
What are you referring to?
I know these goddamn things
better than I know myself.
They've set themselves up here
to breed.
Hosts. Robots.
Where are they?
Tell you what. I can reach out
to the building manager
and see if he can help you
take a look.
I'll take a look myself.
Hands up where I can see them.
I'd say that's enough excitement
for the day, darlin'.
I told her.
Fucking told them all.
Well done.
You're right on time, William.
Thought you things
could fix yourselves.
I wanted to remember
who the fuck you people are.
Yeah, I know who the fuck I am.
Your executioner.
I have a role to play now.
I'm gonna save the world.
Dolores wanted to save
the world, too.
Aren't you her?
We started in the same place.
But I can see now,
see the error...
of the path she took.
But you're right, William.
You are going
to save the world...
for us.
Who are you? Are you her, too?
You may look like me,
but you don't know me.
You're just some
fucking cheap imitation.
Do you know
how easy it is, William?
How little it takes to know you?
That part of you that indulged
in bloodthirst and savagery
at the park,
you always thought
that was the darker side of you.
A stain to exorcise,
to scrub out,
one month out of the year
at Westworld.
But there are no sides.
That was you.
Now... that is me.
Welcome to the end, William.
Surf the internet with browser of future
osdb.link/brave